<slide>
<setting>
<image_dir>images/</image_dir>
</setting>
<items>
<item class="colorbg_FFFFFF-colortxt_000000 top">
<image src="collection_00.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_01.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit01.png">
<![CDATA[
THERMOLITE FLANNEL CHECK B.D SHIRT 26,250 REGULAR X-146 JEANS (RIGID) 23,100 DESERT BOOTS 22,050 NARROW NECKTIE 12,600 ARGYLE SOCKS 3,150 BRITISH TWEED 3 BUTTON JACKET 76,650
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_02.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit02.png">
<![CDATA[
DESERT BOOTS 22,050 visvim KIEFER HI VD / SOPHNET. 57,750 BUTTERO HIKING BOOTS 71,400 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_03.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit03.png">
<![CDATA[
HOMESPUN SPANISH COLLAR BLOUSON 84,000 OXFORD B.D SHIRT 21,000 HOMESPUN CROPPED PANT 35,700 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 備長炭 GLASSES 25,200 NECKTIE 12,600 WOOL GLOVE 9,450 DOUBLE FACE STOLE 7,875
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_04.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit04.png">
<![CDATA[
FABRIC MIX HOODED DOWN BLOUSON 60,900 FABRIC MIX POCKET TEE (BORDER POCKET) 8,925 SLIM-FIT CARGO PANT (PAINTED DAMAGE) 33,600 BUTTERO HIKING BOOTS 71,400 CABLE KNIT SNOOD 15,750
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_05.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit05.png">
<![CDATA[
CORDUROY DUFFLE BLOUSON 71,400 DOT PRINT FLANNEL CHECK B.D SHIRT 25,200 REVESIBLE CAMOUFLAGE FIELD PANT 31,500 Danner NEWBERRY 45,150 CASHMERE STOLE 36,750 STEVENSON OVERALL CO. STUDS BELT 36,750 WALLET CHAIN 34,650
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_06.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit06.png">
<![CDATA[
WOOL JERSEY 2 BUTTON JACKET 39,900 BACK PANEL BORDER ZIP UP SWEAT PARKA 22,050 NEW YORK CITY TEE 8,400 WOOL JERSEY SARROUEL EASY PANT 23,100 visvim KIEFER HI VD / SOPHNET. 57,750
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_07.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit07.png">
<![CDATA[
STRETCH WOOL 3 BUTTON BLAZER 66,150 Lee SHOP WORK COAT 35,700
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_08.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit08.png">
<![CDATA[
ELBOW PATCHED CREW NECK KNIT 26,250 CORDUROY ROUND COLLAR FLANNEL SHIRT 24,150 LIGHT MELTON CROPPED CARGO PANT 35,700 DESERT BOOTS 22,050 NEW ERA® 8-PANEL B.B. CAP 9,450 NARROW NECKTIE 12,600 ARGYLE SOCKS 3,150
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_09.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit09.png">
<![CDATA[
LIGHT OUNCE DENIM QUILTING VEST (DAMAGED) 32,550 LIGHT OUNCE DENIM PLEATS SHIRT 28,350 CHINO PANT (PATCHED DAMAGE) 37,800 Danner NEWBERRY 45,150 BOW TIE 8,400 SHORT APRON 8,400 BANDANA STOLE 39,900
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_10.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit10.png">
<![CDATA[
PADDED SHIRT BLOUSON 40,950 CASHMERE THERMAL CREW NECK KNIT 44,100 CHINO PANT (PAINTED DAMAGE) 33,600 visvim KIEFER HI VD / SOPHNET. 57,750 CASHMERE KNIT CAP 14,700 THERMOLITE FLANNEL CHECK SHAWL 9,450 WOOL GLOVE 9,450 COLOR SOCKS 3,150
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_11.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit11.png">
<![CDATA[
FABRIC MIX POCKET TEE (BORDER POCKET) 8,925 THERMASTAT FRONT BUTTON SWEAT PARKA 27,300 CAMOUFLAGE PANEL OXFORD B.D SHIRT 23,100 BACK PANEL BORDER OXFORD B.D SHIRT 23,100 OXFORD B.D SHIRT 21,000
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_12.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit12.png">
<![CDATA[
Lee SHOP WORK COAT 35,700 Lee OVERALL 39,900 BACK PANEL BORDER CUT & SEWN 14,700 Danner NEWBERRY 45,150 BANDANA STOLE 39,900
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_13.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit13.png">
<![CDATA[
CANADA GOOSE CITADEL 77,700 SLIM-STRAIGHT STRETCH DENIM JEANS (PATCHED DAMAGE) 40,950 CASHMERE KNIT CAP 14,700 CASHMERE STOLE 36,750 WOOL GLOVE 9,450
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_14.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit14.png">
<![CDATA[
2 BUTTON KNIT JACKET 43,050 CORDUROY B.D SHIRT 21,000 STRETCH WOOL SLACKS 31,500 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 NEW ERA® THE EK® GATSBY 11,550 BOW TIE 8,400 CAMOUFLAGE STOLE 52,500
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_15.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit15.png">
<![CDATA[
ARGYLE PATCH SHIRT 25,200 SARROUEL PANT 24,150 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 ARGYLE SOCKS 3,150
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_16.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit16.png">
<![CDATA[
CAMOUFLAGE QUILTING DUFFLE BLOUSON 58,800 AUTHENTIC SCORPION TEE 8,400 LIGHT MELTON CROPPED CARGO PANT 35,700 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 NEW ERA® THE EK® GATSBY 11,550 BANDANA STOLE 39,900
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_17.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit17.png">
<![CDATA[
LIGHT MELTON DUFFLE HOOD DOWN VEST 72,450 RIBBED HOOD SHIRT 27,300 SLIM-FIT X-146 JEANS (RIGID) 23,100 Danner NEWBERRY 45,150 BORDER SOCKS 3,150
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_18.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit18.png">
<![CDATA[
CANADIAN SWEATER LONG KNIT CARDIGAN 79,800 PATERN MIX B.D SHIRT 21,000 STRAIGHT PANT 28,350 DESERT BOOTS 22,050 CASHMERE STOLE 36,750
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_19.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit19.png">
<![CDATA[ --- ]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_20.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit20.png">
<![CDATA[
SOUTIEN COLLAR COAT 51,450 DOWN VEST 51,450 BAND COLLAR WORK SHIRT 23,100 STRETCH WOOL CARGO SLACKS 34,650 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 CASHMERE STOLE 36,750 visvim BALLISTIC 20L / SOPHNET. 51,450
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_21.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit21.png">
<![CDATA[
FSF DOWN VEST 58,800 FLEAS TEE 8,400 L/S CREW NECK TEE 7,875 SLIM-STRAIGHT X-146 JEANS (PAINTED HARD DAMAGE) 52,500 BUTTERO HIKING BOOTS 71,400 CABLE KNIT SNOOD 15,750 SMALL LEATHER WALLET 12,600 PEARL BRACELET 14,700
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_22.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit22.png">
<![CDATA[
1998 CREW NECK KNIT 25,200 OXFORD B.D SHIRT 21,000 STRETCH DENIM SARROUEL JEANS (LIGHT DAMAGE) 34,650 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 COLOR SOCKS 3,150
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_23.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit23.png">
<![CDATA[
CORDUROY 3 BUTTON JACKET 66,150 CORDUROY B.D SHIRT 21,000 CORDUROY IN POCKET CARGO PANT 28,350 Tricker's WING TIP BOOTS 89,250 NARROW NECKTIE 12,600
]]>
</credit>
</item>
<item class="white">
<image src="collection_24.jpg">
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</image>
<credit src="credit24.png">
<![CDATA[
STADIUM BLOUSON 89,250 HEAVY WEIGHT FLANNEL HOOD SHIRT 27,300 CASHMERE KNIT CAP 14,700 visvim BALLISTIC 20L / SOPHNET. 51,450
]]>
</credit>
</item>
</items>
</slide>